Guide to the Darinka Archive, 1973-2010 MSS.340
Fales Library and Special Collections
Darinka Archive
1973-2010
Fales Library and Special Collections
Bugarčić, Gary Ray
MSS.340
12.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 half manuscript box, 9 flat boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 1 flat file folder, and 1 folder in shared housing
Darinka: A Performance Studio was opened in 1984 by Gary Ray Bugarčić (aka Gary Ray). The club served as a venue for artists of all disciplines, including performance, theatre, music, dance, film, video, fine art, and poetry and prose, until its closing in 1987. The archive includes reviews, letters, subject files, contracts, flyers, stencils, photographs, audio and video recordings of performances, and digital data storage disks.
Historical Note
Darinka: A Performance Studio was opened on April 21, 1984 by Gary Ray Bugarčić (aka Gary Ray). The club served as a venue for artists of all disciplines, including performance, theatre, music, dance, film, video, fine art, and poetry and prose. In keeping with the Eastern European roots of the East Village/Lower East Side, the club was named after Gary's mother, who was Croatian born. Darinka is a derivative of the Slavic word dar, meaning "gift."
The club was located at 118 East First Street, two doors down from Avenue A, and had a speakeasy type entrance under the residential stoop of the building. Up to the late 1970s, the space was used as a local Italian Social Club until a fire destroyed it. During the renovation of the space, all the old charred beams were laid in the backyard to provide an urban rustic wood patio enjoyed by patrons during the hot summer months. The interior of the club had a small proscenium stage that was described by many as looking like a live television. A variety of local painters such as James Romberger and Mark Kostabi showed their work on the walls of the club until the permanent murals and stencils were painted. Regular performers included They Might Be Giants (considered the house band), performance artist Steve Buscemi (still a fireman when he started performing), Karen Finley, Jack Smith, Charles Long, William Pope L., Kembra Pfahler, Nick Zedd, Anna Deavere Smith, and John S. Hall. In addition, there were many writers who read during the Sunday prose and poetry nights, including Darius James, Patrick McGrath, Hal Sirowitz, Lynne Tillman, Mark Dery, Nina Zivancevic, Peter Cherches, Bob Holman, Ira Cohen and Taylor Meade.
On June 29, 1985, the NYPD raided the club during a mushroom party and performance by artists David West and Andy Somma. Gary Ray and the bartender, Robin Clements, were arrested for operating an unlicensed bottle club. Several months later Darinka reopened as a private club with Randy Lee Hartwig and John Gernand as managers. As a private club each new member would fill out a membership application card upon entrance. The application cards were kept in a file near the door in case of police inquiry. Membership cards were also distributed.
Darinka was the first home of "The Church of the Little Green Man." The church was founded by conceptual artist Mike Osterhout and had its first service in December of 1986. Darinka closed in May of 1987.
Articles mentioning Darinka have appeared in The Village Voice, New York magazine, High Performance, East Village Eye, Toronto Globe and Mail, The New York Times, and The Drama Review (Spring 1985). The club is also acknowledged in the documentary Gigantic: A Tale Of Two Johns.
Gary Ray Bugarčić, a graduate of The American Academy of Dramatic Arts and SUNY Empire State College, has worked as an actor and stage director in almost every downtown New York theatrical venue and helped develop the off-broadway rock musical Bulldozer: The Ballad of Robert Moses. As a musician, he played in several bands, including State of Desire and The Academy, which performed regularly at CBGB and Danceteria before opening Darinka. After closing the club he toured with Karen Finley in her play The Theory of Total Blame and worked with The Ridiculous Theatrical Company, The Ridge Theatre Company, as well as with Kestutis Nakas and in Jeff Weiss's "Hot Keys." He has also appeared in such indie films as Todd Haynes' Poison and Desperately Seeking Susan. New Blood magazine published his poetry in the 1980s and his photography, including his 3-D lenticular prints, have been exhibited in New York City at The American Academy of Arts and Letters, The Participant Gallery, Max Fish, and 201@105.
Scope and Contents
The Darinka Archive contains material created and collected by Gary Ray Bugarčić, founder of the Darinka Nightclub and performance space. Materials include includes reviews, letters, subject files, contracts, flyers, stencils, photographs, audio and video recordings of performances, and digital data storage disks.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into seven series:
Series I: Darinka Files
Series II: Playbills
Series III: Audio Recordings
Series IV: Video Recordings
Series V: Data Storage
Series VI. Photographs
Series VII. 2015 Accretion
Series I, III, IV, and V are arranged alphabetically. Series II is arranged chronologically. Series VII has not been arranged by an archivist; materials are in the order in which they were received.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Collection transferred in 2012. An addition to the collection was donated in November 2015 by Gary Ray Bugarčić; the accession number associated with this gift is 2015.340. An accretion of one flyer was donated in April 2023; the accession number associated with this accretion is 2023.032.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Photographs.; Videocassettes.; Nightclubs.; Downtown writers.; Alternative rock music.; Audiocassettes.; Punk rock music.; Performance art.; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities).; Printed ephemera.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.); East Village (New York, N.Y.); Bugarčić, Gary Ray
- Series I: Darinka Files
  Scope and Content
  This series contains material created and kept by Darinka. It includes administrative and legal papers, ephemera such as flyers and ticket stubs, press, T-shirts, and photographs.
  - Address Book (1 of 4), circa 1984; cuid21945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address Book (2 of 4), circa 1987; cuid21946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address Book (3 of 4), Undated; cuid21947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Address Book (3 of 4), Undated; cuid21948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Theatre Script, 1986; cuid21949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Becky Letter", 1985; cuid21950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C.V. / Resume / Chronology, Undated; cuid21951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Church of the Little Green Man, Undated; cuid21952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clay Spohn, Undated; cuid21953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clay Spohn - Annotated Bible 11/24/1916, cuid21954 (Box 5)
  - Club Promo Material, Undated; cuid21955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Confessions of a Peyote Eater", Undated; cuid21956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Darinka Arrest Papers, 1985; cuid21957 (Box 1, Folder 11a)
  - "Darinka Flyers: Music and Dance", circa 1984; cuid21958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Darinka Flyers: Performance Etc., circa 1984; cuid21959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Darinka Flyers: Prose / Poetry", 1981-1985; cuid21960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Darinka Flyers - "Yellow Folder", circa 1984; cuid21961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Darinka Leases, 1986-1988; cuid21962 (Box 1, Folder 15a)
  - Darinka Stencils, Undated; cuid21963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Early Darinka Flyers", circa 1986; cuid21964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fast Forward Flyer, undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 20)
  - Film Series posters, circa 1985; cuid21965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Flyers - original, Undated; cuid21966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Headshots, Undated; cuid21967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Huntin'" / "Bodybag", circa 1985; cuid21968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Letters, 1984-1987; cuid21969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letters and contracts, 1981-1989; cuid21970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Misc. Letters", 1981-1990; cuid21971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Posters, Scripts, Announcements, Undated; cuid21972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Programs, flyers, postcards, 1985-1992; cuid21973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Programs, flyers, programs, 1980-2003; cuid21974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Nepotism", 1989; cuid21975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New York City leases, 1990-1991; cuid21976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - New York City subway map, 1977; cuid21977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - New York Magazine, 1985 June 17; cuid21978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Non-Darinka flyers" (CBGB's, etc...), Undated; cuid21979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Organic Extensionism", 1995; cuid21980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Postcards (1 of 2), 1984-1988; cuid21981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Postcards (2 of 2), 1984-1988; cuid21982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Press", circa 1984; cuid21983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Promo cards, circa 1985; cuid21984 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Pull the Lever / PS 122, circa 1994; cuid21985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Reviews / Press", 1985-1992; cuid21986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. etc.", 1985-2003; cuid21987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "S. Past - Ireg.", Undated; cuid21988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tickets / Stubs / Button, 1980-1993; cuid21989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "Tourist Season" shoot, Undated; cuid21990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Typhoid Mary 911 script, Undated; cuid21991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - T-Shirt - "The Love Club", Undated; cuid21992 (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0001)
  - T-Shirt - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. presents Oscar Wilde's Salome", Undated; cuid21993 (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0002)
  - T-Shirt - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. presents Turds in Hell", Undated; cuid21994 (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0003)
  - T-Shirt - "Viva Carlo! Viva Livertad!" David Wojnarowicz illustration, Undated; cuid21995 (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0004)
  - "This Performance Sold Out" sign, Undated; 340.2.0005; 1 item one sign (Object ID: 340.2.0005)
    Information signs.
- Series II: Playbills
  This series contains collected playbills, including several from the Ridiculous Theatrical Company.
  - Playbills (1 of 5), 1970-1990; cuid21996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Playbills (2 of 5), 1991-1995; cuid21997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Playbills (3 of 5), 1991-1995; cuid21998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Playbills (4 of 5), 1996-2010; cuid21999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Playbills (5 of 5), 1996-2010; cuid22000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  This series contains all audio recordings stored on magnetic audiocassettes. It includes live performances at Darinka, compilation tapes, demo tapes, and miscellaneous recordings organized alphabetically by artist or project title.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Performance
    This subseries contains audio recordings of performances at Darinka and other venues.
    - A: The Academy, "Windows Closed" "Sidewalk" "Work Tape" "1st Time"; B: Jaco Pastorius "Live!" "with Great Harp Player", 1983 July; 340.0001 (Box 7, Cassette 340.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 56 min.
    - "Academy I copyright tape", 1984 October 1; ID: 340.0002 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0002)
      Original format: audiocassette
    - The Academy - CBGB's, 1983 October 20; ID: 340.0003 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0003)
    - A: Academy 12-3-83 CBGB's; B:12-3-83 cont, 10-20-83, 1983 December 3, 1983 October 20; ID: 340.0004 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0004)
    - Fives; The Academy, 1983 October 9; ID: 340.0005 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0005)
    - "Academy with EYAL ", 1983 December; ID: 340.0006 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0006)
    - The Academy 12-3-83 CBGB's., 1983 December 3; ID: 340.0007 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0007)
    - Academy 12-28-83 CBGB's, 1983 December 28; ID: 340.0008 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0008)
    - The Academy - Cosmic Pig Roast, 1983 December; ID: 340.0009 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0009)
    - The Academy. 4-Track recorded at Dubway Studio., undated; ID: 340.0010 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0010)
    - The Academy - 4-Track recorded at Dubway Studio., 1983; ID: 340.0011 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0011)
    - The Academy. CBGB's., 1983 October 20; ID: Cassette ID: 340.0012 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0012)
    - The Academy live., 1983; ID: 340.0013 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0013)
    - The Academy Copyright, 1983; ID: 340.0014 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0014)
    - The Academy CBGB's., 1983 March 10; ID: 340.0015 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0015)
    - Academy CBGB's., 1984 March 10; ID: 340.0016 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0016)
    - Academy. CBGB's., 1984 April 6; ID: 340.0017 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0017)
    - "Academy. 1st Rehearsel", 1984 July; ID: 340.0018 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0018)
    - Academy of Nuns. CBGB's. Pressure Point, Down the Line. Jam., 1984 August; ID: 340.0019 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0019)
    - Academy CB's., 1984 December 7; ID: 340.0020 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0020)
    - "Academy of Nuns (Master)", undated; ID: 340.0021 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0021)
    - The Academy: 2 Songs., 1983; ID: 340.0022 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0022)
    - "Statue with Dave Gerad." Academy., 1984 December 4; ID: 340.0023 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0023)
    - Academy - "Woodstone Project", undated; ID: 340.0024 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0024)
    - The Academy, undated; ID: 340.0025 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0025)
    - A: Academy; B: Rehearsal; Piano Music; Academy Rehearsal; Bill and Steve, undated; ID: 340.0026 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0026)
    - Academy. Al - Steve Logan. Bill - Norm., undated; ID: 340.0027 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0027)
    - The Academy, "Lonesome Runner", undated; ID: 340.0028 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0028)
    - The Academy - 2 Songs., undated; ID: 340.0029 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0029)
    - The Academy Demo tape, undated; ID: 340.0030 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0030)
    - The Academy: 2 Songs, undated; ID: 340.0031 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0031)
    - 4 Track - Broken Glass Live, undated; ID: 340.0032 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0032)
    - "Chump Change with Bad Vocals", undated; ID: 340.0033 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0033)
    - "Cowboy Work Tape", undated; ID: 340.0034 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0034)
    - "TUBOB I", undated; ID: 340.0035 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0035)
    - Big Bang Live at the Batcave, undated; ID: 340.0036 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0036)
    - Church of the Little Green Man, undated; 340.0037 (Box 7, Cassette 340.0037)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 94 min.
    - Church of the Little Green Man Radio, undated; ID: 340.0038 (Box 7, Cassette 340.0038)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration:: 94 min.
    - Epileptic Fitness "I-II", undated; ID: 340.0039 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0039)
    - Epileptic Fitness "III - IV", undated; ID: 340.0040 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0040)
    - Edward L. Gordon "Colage", 1978; ID: 340.0041 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0041)
    - Karen Finley Interview, undated; ID: 340.0042 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0042)
    - Jickets, undated; ID: 340.0043 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0043)
    - Hugo Largo at Darinka, 1985; ID: 340.0044 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0044)
    - Hayes Lazar/Vocals, undated; ID: 340.0045 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0045)
    - Haze Laser "Rock of My Heart", undated; ID: 340.0046 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0046)
    - Over-Knife Sensation Luxury Knives, 1982 April 18; ID: 340.0047 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0047)
    - Ambient Laragi, undated; ID: 340.0048 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0048)
    - Luxury Knives CBGB's, 1983 January 14; ID: 340.0049 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0049)
    - Fall 82 Knives with Peter Earth, 1982; ID: 340.0050 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0050)
    - New Year's Eve Luxury Knives, 1982 December 31; ID: 340.0051 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0051)
    - Gary and Jeff Demo, 1983 February; ID: 340.0052 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0052)
    - Luxury Knives Rehearsal, 1982 February 13; ID: 340.0053 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0053)
    - Luxury Knives, 1983 March 13; ID: 340.0054 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0054)
    - Luxury Knives, 1983 May; ID: 340.0055 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0055)
    - Early Work Tape Luxury Knives, undated; ID: 340.0056 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0056)
    - Luxury Knives, "Buried Alive" etc., undated; ID: 340.0057 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0057)
    - Luxury Knives G.T., undated; ID: 340.0058 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0058)
    - Luxury Knives - Sunday Knives, undated; ID: 340.0059 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0059)
    - Luxury Knives, 5 Song Demo Tapes, undated; ID: 340.0060 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0060)
    - Luxury Knives - Psycho Jamboree, undated; ID: 340.0061 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0061)
    - Purple Geezus, "Jennifer Polanski", 1988; ID: 340.0062 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0062)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    - Purple Geezus, "V.S.O.P.", 1987; ID: 340.0063 (Box 7, Media ID: 340.0063)
    - Sonorexia, undated; ID: 340.0064 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0064)
    - State of Desire, CBGB's, 1982 January; ID: 340.0065 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0065)
    - State of Desire CBGB's, 1982 June 12; ID: 340.0066 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0066)
    - State of Desire Rehearsal New Tunes, undated; ID: 340.0067 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0067)
    - State of Desire, undated; ID: 340.0068 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0068)
    - State of Desire Rehearsal, undated; ID: 340.0069 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0069)
    - State of Desire with Messages, undated; ID: 340.0070 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0070)
    - Trumbull High School, 1974 May; ID: 340.0071 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0071)
    - Sum 1 Ron Schlossberg JAM, undated; ID: 340.0072 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0072)
    - Sum 1 with Haze, undated; ID: 340.0073 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0073)
    - Sum 1, undated; ID: 340.0074 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0074)
    - They Might Be Giants, 1985; ID: 340.0075 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0075)
      Original format: audiocassette, Duration: 6 min.
    - They Might Be Giants, 1985; ID: 340.0076 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0076)
      Original format: audiocassette, Duration: 45 min.; Preservation Note: Side 1: The beginning of the first song is clipped on the original tape and the digital copy.
    - They Might Be Giants Inter, undated; ID: 340.0077 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0077)
      Scope and Contents
      The content contains answering machine messages and experimental music recorded backwards.
    - They Might Be Giants, "They Got Lost", undated; ID: 340.0078 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0078)
    - Walter Thompson - WKCR, 1984 December; ID: 340.0079 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0079)
    - "Toyko Tower" (sp), undated; ID: 340.0080 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0080)
    - Tokyo Tower - Bass Line, undated; ID: 340.0081 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0081)
    - Tokyo Tower - Phone Messages, undated; ID: 340.0082 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0082)
    - "Tokyko Tower" (sp), 1989 March 6; ID: 340.0083 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0083)
    - Tokyo Tower, undated; ID: 340.0084 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0084)
    - Circus Assault - Master, undated; ID: 340.0085 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0085)
    - Circus Assault - Show tape, 1986 September; ID: 340.0086 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0086)
    - Disco House - Subliminal, undated; ID: 340.0087 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0087)
    - Bass, undated; ID: 340.0088 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0088)
    - Kung Fu Fighting, undated; ID: 340.0089 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0089)
    - Take 1, undated; ID: 340.0090 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0090)
    - B + B + Me, undated; ID: 340.0091 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0091)
    - Patrick, undated; ID: 340.0092 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0092)
    - Decca-Dance, 1983; ID: 340.0093 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0093)
    - Curtis Gone Bad, undated; ID: 340.0094 (Box 8, Media ID: ID: 340.0094)
      Currently unavailable until photoduplication occurs.
    - Jeff Music Ideas, undated; ID: 340.0095 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0095)
    - 3 Song Demo Jeff Ideas, undated; ID: 340.0096 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0096)
    - Jeff 5/28, undated; ID: 340.0097 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0097)
    - Peter, undated; ID: 340.0098 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0098)
    - Avant-Garde, undated; ID: 340.0099 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0099)
  - Subseries B: Darinka Music
    This subseries contains compilation tapes of music played at Darinka.
    - Art of Noise, undated; ID: 340.0100 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0100)
    - Assorted Party music, undated; ID: 340.0101 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0101)
    - Sonny Averona, "Live At Palumbo's", undated; ID: 340.0102 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0102)
    - Adrian Belew, undated; ID: 340.0103 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0103)
    - B-Funk, undated; ID: 340.0104 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0104)
    - Pay Back, undated; ID: 340.0105 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0105)
    - Cab, undated; ID: 340.0106 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0106)
    - Club Funk, undated; ID: 340.0107 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0107)
    - Club Tape, undated; ID: 340.0108 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0108)
    - Gato Barbieri, undated; ID: 340.0109 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0109)
    - Elvis Costello, undated; ID: 340.0110 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0110)
    - Sam Cooke, undated; ID: 340.0111 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0111)
    - Dance I, undated; ID: 340.0112 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0112)
    - Dance Tape II, undated; ID: 340.0113 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0113)
    - Jazz Dance III, undated; ID: 340.0114 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0114)
    - Dance IV, undated; ID: 340.0115 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0115)
    - Dance IV, undated; ID: 340.0116 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0116)
    - Dance Up and Down, undated; ID: 340.0117 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0117)
    - Dark and Arabian Feel, undated; ID: 340.0118 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0118)
    - Miles Davis - Terry Gibbs, undated; ID: 340.0119 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0119)
    - Diva, undated; ID: 340.0120 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0120)
    - Diva Original Soundtrack, undated; ID: 340.0121 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0121)
    - DJ Mix: New Order, Cocteau Twins, Soul Sonic, undated; ID: 340.0122 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0122)
    - Eurythmics, undated; ID: 340.0123 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0123)
    - Fun Boy 3, "Colour Field", undated; ID: 340.0124 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0124)
    - Fun Boy 3, "Waiting", undated; ID: 340.0125 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0125)
    - D. Bowie, "Pinups", undated; ID: 340.0126 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0126)
    - Gay Tunes For Gary, undated; ID: 340.0127 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0127)
    - Tom Waits, undated; ID: 340.0128 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0128)
    - Joe Jackson, OMD…, undated; ID: 340.0129 (Box 8, Media ID: 340.0129)
    - George Jones, "The Race Is On", undated; ID: 340.0130 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0130)
    - King Pleasure, undated; ID: 340.0131 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0131)
    - Fela Kuti, undated; ID: 340.0132 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0132)
    - On the Run I Waited, undated; ID: 340.0133 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0133)
    - London Radio, undated; ID: 340.0134 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0134)
    - Lounge Lizards/Blue Hawaii, undated; ID: 340.0135 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0135)
    - Motown Gold, undated; ID: 340.0136 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0136)
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Mr. Lee, undated; ID: 340.0137 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0137)
    - Murray the K Show, 1963; ID: 340.0138 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0138)
    - New Order, Promenaders, undated; ID: 340.0139 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0139)
    - New Sounds, undated; ID: 340.0140 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0140)
    - OMD - PIL, Wall of Voodoo, undated; ID: 340.0141 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0141)
    - Party Mix, undated; ID: 340.0142 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0142)
    - SALSA, undated; ID: 340.0143 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0143)
    - Police, Patsy Cline, Crazy, undated; ID: 340.0144 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0144)
    - Elvis Presley, undated; ID: 340.0145 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0145)
    - Throbbing Gristle, undated; ID: 340.0146 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0146)